Jason is ready for adulthood. His grandpa isn't.
Dirty Grandpa is a comedy film directed by Dan Mazer.
Jason Kelly is one week away from marrying his boss's uber-controlling daughter,
putting him on the fast track for a partnership at the law firm.
However, when the straight-laced Jason is tricked into driving his foul-mouthed grandfather,
Dick, to Daytona for spring break, his pending nuptials are suddenly in jeopardy.
Between riotous frat parties, bar fights, and an epic night of karaoke, Dick is on a
quest to live his life to the fullest and bring Jason along for the ride.
Dick Kelly, played by Robert De Niro.
Jason Kelly, played by Zac Efron.
Lenore, played by Aubrey Plaza.
Shadia, played by Zoey Deutch.
Meredith Goldstein, played by Julianne Hough.
David Kelly, played by Dermot Mulroney.
Dirty Grandpa is a 2016 American comedy film about a lawyer who
drives his grandfather to Florida during spring break.
The film was directed by Dan Mazer and written by John Phillips.
It stars Robert De Niro and Zac Efron in the leading roles, with Aubrey Plaza,
Zoey Deutch, Julianne Hough and Dermot Mulroney in supporting roles.
It was filmed on location in Atlanta from January 19 to May 9, 2015.
The film was theatrically released on January 22, 2016, by Lionsgate.
It grossed $105 million worldwide, and was panned by critics, several
of whom called it the worst film they had ever seen.
The film explores themes of funeral, golf, grandfather, road trip, crude humor.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.